<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>en.thebinary.org</title>
    <link href="https://en.thebinary.org/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://en.thebinary.org" />
    <updated>2024-10-26T22:22:05+03:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Ilias Giannakopoulos</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://en.thebinary.org</id>

    <entry>
        <title>....post 1..ποστ 1....</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ilias Giannakopoulos</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://en.thebinary.org/posts/post-1/"/>
        <id>https://en.thebinary.org/posts/post-1/</id>

        <updated>2024-10-09T20:13:47+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    ....post EN..post EL.... 123
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>....post EN..post EL....</p>
<p>123</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Mission: Brussels 2023</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ilias Giannakopoulos</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://en.thebinary.org/posts/mission-brussels-2023/"/>
        <id>https://en.thebinary.org/posts/mission-brussels-2023/</id>
        <media:content url="https://en.thebinary.org/media/posts/3/2023_MISSION_BRUSSELS_2023_1800x1200-2.jpg" medium="image" />
            <category term="Mission"/>
            <category term="Featured"/>
            <category term="Brussels"/>

        <updated>2023-11-13T18:27:00+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://en.thebinary.org/media/posts/3/2023_MISSION_BRUSSELS_2023_1800x1200-2.jpg" alt="Mission: Brussels 2023" />
                    Heinrich Böll Stiftung organised the Media Freedom Visit 6 to 9 Nov 2023 in Brussels to dive into the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://en.thebinary.org/media/posts/3/2023_MISSION_BRUSSELS_2023_1800x1200-2.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="Mission: Brussels 2023" /></p>
                <p><strong>Heinrich Böll Stiftung organised the Media Freedom Visit 6 to 9 Nov 2023 in Brussels to dive into the challenges of Democracy in the EU.</strong></p>
<p>In a world where information is a potent currency, the knowledge, the need for freedom in journalism stands as the guardian of truth and democracy. Last week, we had the privilege of attending an enlightening set of sessions in Brussels, organised by the esteemed political foundation <a href="https://www.boell.de/en" title="Heinrich Böll Stiftung" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Heinrich Böll Stiftung</a>. This gathering aimed to delve into the intricate web of challenges faced by journalists worldwide and explore the indispensable role they play in shaping our societies and the future.</p>
<p>The initiative started with a poignant acknowledgment of the critical times we live in, where the very essence of journalism is under threat. The <a href="https://www.boell.de/en" title="Heinrich Böll foundation" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Heinrich Böll foundation</a>, known for its commitment to promoting democracy, civil and human rights, and environmental sustainability, set the stage for a thought-provoking discussion on the state of journalism and the various forces influencing it.</p>
<p>Renowned journalists and media experts took center stage to share their experiences and insights, ask questions and raise the bar for the future. Respected professionals, from the borders to the heart of political turmoil, shared the view of their stories, painting a vivid picture of the challenges journalists face in their pursuit of truth. The discussions ranged from the rise of misinformation to the dangers of censorship, SLAPPs, monitoring and digital surveillance, emphasising the need for a robust defense of journalistic freedom focusing in digital rights, the protection of personal data, access to information and the freedom of expression. </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Click at Aegean Docs 2022</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Binary Newsroom</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://en.thebinary.org/posts/click-at-aegean-docs-2022/"/>
        <id>https://en.thebinary.org/posts/click-at-aegean-docs-2022/</id>
        <media:content url="https://en.thebinary.org/media/posts/4/2022_CLICK_AEGEANDOCS.jpg" medium="image" />
            <category term="Press-Release"/>
            <category term="Picks"/>

        <updated>2022-09-20T12:00:00+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://en.thebinary.org/media/posts/4/2022_CLICK_AEGEANDOCS.jpg" alt="Click at Aegean Docs 2022" />
                    Friday 30 September, at 9.30 pm at the Municipal Theater of Mitilini, the non-profit organisation The Binary presents its&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://en.thebinary.org/media/posts/4/2022_CLICK_AEGEANDOCS.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="Click at Aegean Docs 2022" /></p>
                <p>Friday 30 September, at 9.30 pm at the Municipal Theater of Mitilini, the non-profit organisation The Binary presents its short film: "Click, a story about digital rights" directed by Yiannis Christoforou.<br><br>The film was chosen to be screened by the 10th Aegean Docs Festival and presents, in an understandable way, the necessity of recognising the digital rights of citizens, many of whom (as you will see in Binary's video) do not know why they concern them.<br><br>Click is a film on the story of digital rights. In short, it's you in a film.<br><br>It starts with human existence and carries you into the jarring effect of the digital world, reaching to the point where you are called to make the decision about the future. All these on a journey full of light that reveals the "invisible" and the "intangible", in a digital world that is absolutely real, between stars and beautiful screens, between mathematics and emotions, between everything you have already lived and what shapes your future, between you and your mirror.<br><br>This is a story about the anthropocentric nature of technology that takes you by the hand for a quick ride through a journey you have never been through, with the brightest and sometimes the darkest views of the technological cosmogony. <br><br>A journey into the other side of the "Wonderland", where everything runs faster than life. Where everything changes in a “click".</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>A Voter&#x27;s Guide and 7 Tips to Detox Your Data, in partnership with Tactical Tech</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Binary Newsroom</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://en.thebinary.org/posts/a-voters-guide-and-7-tips-to-detox-your-data-in-partnership-with-tactical-tech/"/>
        <id>https://en.thebinary.org/posts/a-voters-guide-and-7-tips-to-detox-your-data-in-partnership-with-tactical-tech/</id>
        <media:content url="https://en.thebinary.org/media/posts/5/2022_VOTERS_GUIDE_TACTICALTECH.jpg" medium="image" />
            <category term="Press-Release"/>
            <category term="Picks"/>
            <category term="Partnership"/>

        <updated>2022-08-19T12:20:00+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://en.thebinary.org/media/posts/5/2022_VOTERS_GUIDE_TACTICALTECH.jpg" alt="A Voter&#x27;s Guide and 7 Tips to Detox Your Data" />
                    Voter’s Guide is a set of resources designed to promote citizens’ critical thinking about the use of their personal&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://en.thebinary.org/media/posts/5/2022_VOTERS_GUIDE_TACTICALTECH.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="A Voter&#x27;s Guide and 7 Tips to Detox Your Data" /></p>
                <div class="row voffset-clear-md">
<div class="col bgc-white">
<p class="mg-md tc-dark-jungle-green p-bloc-story-style">Voter’s Guide is a set of resources designed to promote citizens’ critical thinking about the use of their personal data by political groups to influence public opinion, elections, and other political participation.</p>
</div>
<div class="col bgc-white"> </div>
</div>
<div class="row voffset-clear-md">
<div class="col bgc-white">
<p class="mg-md tc-dark-jungle-green p-206-style">Across the world, data on citizens is being collected, traded and utilised to influence their political views . Despite increased attention in recent years, it is still difficult to access information about the industry actors or the technologies that they use to sway citizens' political views. This project aims to increase accessibility and understanding to strengthen civic capacity to engage with politics.</p>
</div>
<div class="col bgc-white"> </div>
</div>
<div class="row voffset-clear-md">
<div class="col bgc-white">
<p class="mg-md tc-dark-jungle-green p-206-style">In partnership with Tactical Tech, the Voter’s Guide pack contents are based on the extensive research conducted by “Data and Politics Team” with partners from over 20 countries on how technology and personal data is used to influence political opinion.</p>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
